Yes, tea! That's my trade!
Quincy Endicott's Health Tea.
Your tea sounds good.
Hah, never touch the stuff myself.
Bleh. Me either.
Ha ha! Yes!
It's all for the money, yes!
The money takes my mind off my troubles!
The deep, soul-crushing loneliness.
Yes, the more money I make,
the bigger my mansion gets,
the more lost I feel.
Why, this house is so big,
I sometimes don't even know where
or who I am!
Yeah, well, I'm glad your...
nephews here were able to pay a visit.
Yeah!
Yes, what a... what a pleasure it is to have company...
A perfect pleasure!
A perfect pleasure, lads!
A per... yes, yes.
- Uh huh!
- Perfect! Perfect!
- Yeah, yeah.
♪ A most Perfect pleasure, Heather... ♪
Um, Beatrice,
w-why are you pretending I'm this guy's nephew?
We need money.
You're scamming him?
I was thinking more like
flat-out stealing from him.
What?! No way!
Why not?
We already stole a horse.
Hey, guys.
No, we didn't.
Fred's a talking horse.
He can do whatever he wants.
I want to steal.
Huh! What?!
You guys are bonkers!
If we're going to Adelaide's,
- we need two cents
- Mm-hmm.
Well, you guys do what you...
...two cents?
- Only two cents?
- Yeah, we need two pennies
to take the ferry to Adelaide's pasture.
Ha ha! Come everyone!
Let us retire to the parlor and enjoy
my unnecessary excess of wealth and luxury.
Well, maybe he just has some loose change somewhere
he wouldn't mind us taking.
- Uh huh, mm-hm
- Mm-hm, mm-hm, mm-hm.
Behold, nephew, the majesty of wealth!
Ooh!
What was that?! Uh...
What's wrong unkie Endicott?
Your forehead is all sweaty.
M-My nerves. My...
my... my ner...
my nerves are a bust these days.
How come?
Uh, yes, yes. Maybe it would be...
good to talk to someone.
Well, y...
Actually, it all began one day
when I was exploring
my exceedingly large and labyrinthine manor here.
I happened upon a section of the house I didn't even recall building.
Uh ha ha ha!
Isn't that funny?
Must've been the old wing.
But it was lit in a rather sort of
eer... eerie ... eerie light.
And I pressed on, and then I-
I saw the painting of the most
beautiful woman I've ever seen,
and that's when...
things took a rather strange turn.
From that day on, I was obsessed with the woman in the portrait.
She con... consumed my every thought.
I'd fallen in love, ha ha!
...with a ghost!
Ohhhh.
It's too big. Get a grip.
Oh, I must sound crazy, mustn't I?
Perhaps it's time for you all
to leave my treasure-filled home.
- No!
Yeah, unkie!
I want to see the ghost!
Ohh, how I long to see her
just once again, as well, yes.
To the painting!
Yes. Yes.
Ooh, boy! Ghost hunt!
Fred, go with them. (Buy me some time.)
(While I'm at it,)
I'll steal other stuff, too!
We're supposed to just be looking for loose change.
That's what I'm ...
Oops. That's what I'm doing.
Well, let's try not
to break any more ...
Gah!
Oh, hey.
Hey, you didn't check the armoire.
Tap, tap, tap...
Huh! Endicott's back
Hide!
Tap, tap, tap. Tap, taptaptap.
Tap.
- Is that the portrait?
- No.
Is that the portrait?
No.
Look, w-w-why don't I-
I just tell you when we reach the portrait.
Okay, what's the matter, unkie?
You seem tense.
You know me well, nephew.
Yes, the truth is..
I'm frightened.
Of a ghost?
Ghosts are just floaty things.
Oh, no, no, not afraid of the ghost.
I mean I'm afraid what... what... what..
if there is no ghost?
What if I'm on the... on the...
on the... on the brink of...
hmm...
madness!
Maybe the doctors were right.
Come along, boys! Back to the parlor.
The parlor!?
What would anyone go the parlor for?
There's nobody in the parlor...
certainly nobody after your money.
Yeah, no giving up now, old man.
It's got to be a ghost!
But h-how can you be so certain?
'Cause I really, really want to see a ghost...
- ...really bad.
- Oh.
Whew.
Okay, I think they're gone.
- Beatrice? You there?
- Bah! Yes, smart guy.
Start searching for change.
Uh, I can't see anything in here.
Well, I-I don't think
these coats have pockets.
Check the lining. Maybe somebody sewed money
- into the fabric.
- Nope.
Do people even do that?
I've done it on my clothes.
You wear clothes?
Like a little bird vest or something?
hehe, or little bows?
When I was a human, fool!
You used to be human?
Did I know that?
I-I don't think I knew that.
Jiminy Cricket! Let's just find some coins, all right?
Open the door.
It's stuck.
Well, guess we have to spend some quality time together.
Help!
The greenhouse.
This is where I grow my
camellia for testing new teas.
Perhaps we should savor the ...
the quiet tranquility of this...
this place.
Tap tap tap, tap tap.
Ah!
A ghost!
WAAAAHHH!!!
I can't do it!
Uncle Endicott, it's
just a...
funny chicken.
Yes, o-one of my
prize-winning roasting peacocks.
Yes, with all this love in my brain, I, uh...
forgot to feed them.
It's almost as though I've lost my...
mind!
We can look for that after we find our ghost
Heave-ho!
Yes, yes. Heave-ho.
Into the abyss...
never to return.
Um, anyone want
to go back to the parlor?
Hey. Are you still there?
Yes, Wirt. I'm still here.
So, how did you become a bluebird?
Hey, what's that?
Don't change the subject.
Hmm.
There's a breeze coming out of here.
Oh, yeah.
- Whoa!
- What?!
A secret entrance!
So,
about your dark secret.
Hey, how about you tell me your dark secrets instead, huh?
My secrets are too secret.
Hey, look. Light.
Whoa. Now who's
avoiding the question?
You.
Fine!
I threw a rock at a bluebird,
and it cursed me and my family,
and now we're all bluebirds.
Happy? Now you go.
Whoa. Your whole family?
Yeah.
Is that why you're going to Adelaide?
To fix things?
That was the plan, but...
Yeah, that was the plan.
It'll all work out.
All I know is I am never going back till I can make them human again.
I'd do pretty much anything.
All right.
My turn, huh? Okay.
Well, it's weird to admit it, but, well, I...
I have this crush on this girl.
Mm-hmm.
That's all.
That's all?!
And I think about her a lot,
and I play clarinet.
Wirt! You got to be kidding me.
And I secretly whisper poetry to myself in my room at night.
Wirt, that stuff's not weird.
Those are just...
well, the poetry thing is weird.
But those are just character traits.
- You played clarinet?
- Sort of.
What else do you do?
I don't know.
Uh... hey. Does this
room look different to you?
Uh, how so?
It's like French Rococo style.
That doesn't really seem in line with Endicott's Georgian sensibilities.
How... what?
Who on Earth am I talking to right now?
Should I not know that sort of stuff?
Endicott probably just built
it without thinking, right?
Or... whoa! Yeah.
W-What if the ghost he was talking about was actually...
This is the room where...
the room where I first saw her.
Whooooooa...
Just a bedroom?
Just a bedroom, my nephew?
This is the chamber of mine own
true love, and here she stands,
hovering above us
like the blinding sun.
Hmm. No ghost?
No ghost?! Then I am...
mad.
Don't be mad.
Heeeey.
What's this suspicious mess over here?
It looks like there was a struggle...
a violent struggle.
What are you implying,
my equine friend?
Nothing, nothing. I'm just...
Endicott is a crazed lunatic who did away with the lady of the house
and is now pretending to own the place!
What?!
Who do you think you are, making accusa...
I see it now.
You're after my money.
Do you the things that I did for this money?
T-The things these filthy hands have done to make this money?!
I'll never steal again,
I swear. I'll get an honest job.
And what say you... nephew?
Uh, I'm confused.
Well, then...
OoOoOoOoOo...
She comes for me!
Wait, unkie!
Face your fears!
Huh!
Mr. Endicott? Are you all right?
Psst! Ghost.
What do you want with me, spirit?
Spirit? But you're the ghost.
My lady, I assure you
I am flesh and blood and I...
I welcome you to my home.
Your home? Good sir,
you're in my home.
Impossible!
Look here.
You see?
This is my camellia garden
for my tea company.
Margueritte Grey?!
Why, with all due respect, madam,
this is my tea garden.
Quincy Endicott?!
Your guys' mansions are so huge
they're actually connected.
So you... you mean that beautiful ghost
was really just...
That dashing specter was really just...
- My business competitor?
Well, Greg, my boy,
I can't thank you enough for helping me to face my fears.
You're a... you're a sweet boy with good sense.
Take this penny...
and start your fortune.
And here's one from me, as well.
Hey, nice.
Now we can ride the ferry.
Well, everybody,
I think it's time we head to
Adelaide of the pasture,
the good woman of the woods.
Uh, what about you, Fred?
Are you coming with us?
No, thanks. I've got a real job now
as an official tea horse.
Well, then I guess that's it.
Off you go, the lot of you.
Goodbye.
- Goodbye!
- Goodbye.
Goodbye.
And don't forget to
buy Endicott brand tea.
Hey, Wirt.
You did good back there.
Yeah?
You had a lot more going for you than I thought.
Huh?
Greg! Our pennies!
Why did you do that?!
'Cause uncle Endicott
pegged me all wrong ...
I've got no "cents,"
no "cents" at all.